<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ShopzterProject</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">SplashScreen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dashboard">DashboardActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="story">Story</string>
    <string name="teaching">Teaching</string>
    <string name="meditation">Meditation</string>
    <string name="excercise">Exercise</string>
    <string name="journal">Journal</string>
    <string name="day_one_meditation_str">On an even subtler level, all the parts of your body are made of molecules, atoms and sub-atomic particles, and these are in constant motion. Try to really get a feeling for the change that is taking place each moment in your body…. Then turn your attention to your mind. It too is composed of many parts— thoughts, perceptions, feelings, memories, images— following one after the other, ceaselessly. Spend a few minutes simply observing the ever-changing flow of experiences in your mind, like someone looking out of a window onto a busy street, watching the cars and pedestrians passing by. Don’t cling to anything that you see in your mind, don’t judge or make comments— just observe, and try to get a sense of the impermanent, ever-changing nature of your mind. After reflecting on the impermanence of your inner world—your own body and mind— extend your awareness to the outer world. Think about your immediate surroundings: the cushion, mat or bed you are sitting on; the floor, walls, windows and ceiling of the room you are sitting in; the furniture and other objects in the room. Consider that each of these things, although appearing solid and static, is actually a mass of tiny particles whizzing around in space. Stay with that awareness of the impermanent, constantly-changing nature of these things. Then let your awareness travel further out, beyond the walls of your room. Think of other people: their bodies and minds are also constantly changing, not staying the same for even one moment. The same is true of all living beings, such as animals, birds and insects. Think of all the inanimate objects in the world and in the universe: houses, buildings, roads, cars, trees, mountains, oceans and rivers, the earth itself, the sun, moon and stars. All of these things, being composed of atoms and other minute particles, are constantly changing, every moment, every millisecond. Nothing stays the same without changing. While you are meditating, if at any point you experience a clear, strong feeling of the every - changing nature of things, stop the thinking or analyzing process, and hold your attention firmly on this feeling. Concentrate on it for as long as possible, without thinking of anything else or letting your mind be distracted. When the feeling fades or your attention starts to wander, again return to analyzing the impermanent nature of things.</string>
</resources>
